Speaker 2: Well guess what? I'm the threat. We the smart black men that don't care about your lives.
Speaker 3: So you say he's not doing anything for the people right now as the President of the United States? Lowest black unemployment. Lowest Asian unemployment. Lowest Latino unemployment. Hundred billion dollars towards black communities. First step back, jail reform bill. Stock market at his all-time high. Best economy we've ever had. These are all facts. You can Google it
Speaker 4: right now.
-
Speaker 4: Has he done to benefit the country? - I just told you. - Repeat it.
Speaker 5: We'll one day live in a nation where they will not be judged
by the
Speaker 5: color of their skin, but by the
Speaker 6: content of their character. I have a dream for you. -
Look, this
Speaker 7: guy, he say he likes my outfit. Look, check him out. He say he likes
my outfit. -
Speaker 8: If I want it, I go get it. Can't nobody stop me.
Speaker 8: All right, Republicans is about can.
Speaker 9: Republic can. We can do what we want. The only enemy you have is yourself, and that's
reality. If you
Speaker 9: black and you a Democrat,
Speaker 10: you're an idiot. You only a slave if you want to be a slave. It's a choice. If you don't choose to be a slave, you're not a slave. Y'all like Obama because he was smooth? All criminals are smooth, man. They don't want to represent their country. Get out of here then. We're Americans. I'm telling you, it changes the whole narrative. Democrats, not Republicans. We took you out of slavery.
Speaker 10: This racist ass president seems to be doing a lot for the minorities. Y'all want to pay this narrative, make white people feel guilty for stuff they had nothing to do with. That's retarded. But I'm black. I'm not supposed to be talking like this. That means I'm dumb. That means I can't do anything. That means I have to think like everybody else. We have to be sheep. They don't even have to sell
you they
Speaker 10: vote. They don't even got to buy it from
Speaker 12: you 'cause black people just give it
away. How you get
Speaker 12: so much favor on your
Woman 13: side.
Woman 13: Accept them as your Lord and Savior, I replied. That's your love, that neighbor, not divide. I'm a ride, that's on God. His light shine the brightest in the dark. Single mothers know they got my heart. And all my brothers locked up on the yard. You can still be anything you want
to be.
Woman 13: Went from one and four to one and three.
Speaker 14: What's up, everybody?
Check
Speaker 15: this out man. You know I always do this, I always walk around on stage and talk my junk and stuff like that, but this time we gonna try something different. Everybody always
Speaker 14: tells me, they're like, "King Face, you should run for office or something." And I was like, "I don't know." But I was like, you know what? I'll take this moment to practice as if I was running on stage, all right? Come on up.
Where's my
Speaker 14: jacket at? Let me get presidential
on 'em.
Let me get presidential. They ain't turn the mic on for
Speaker 16: me?
Speaker 14: Oh, there you
go.
That's
Speaker 16: like, wait, y'all don't want me to talk? OK.
Speaker 14: That's a little too loud
for me
Speaker 14: there. What's up, everybody? How are
you? See, I don't know how I'm going
Speaker 15: to do it on stage. I don't know if I should do the Bill Clinton. I did not have sexual
Speaker 17: relations with that woman, Monica Lewinsky, or should I do Minnie
Mike? Should I do Minnie
Speaker 18: Mike?
Nah, but
Speaker 19: let's start off by this, let's talk about the word "can't."
Speaker 15: The word I feel is the most dangerous word in the English language. This word has been used to keep people down, especially the black community. We were told you're black. You can't make it in America. You can't own anything. You can't get loans from banks. You can't live in nice places and you can't start
businesses.
Everything
Speaker 15: that deters black people from advancing starts with can't, can't, can't. It made me realize the word can't is very dangerous because it causes self-doubt and also stops your brain from working. So you can't figure out solutions unless it's put in front of another dangerous word called lose, as in can't lose.
And we as a community need
Speaker 15: to adopt that can't lose attitude. I've adopted that attitude a long time ago.
Speaker 15: Look at me. Yeah, look at me
right there.
Speaker 20: Jeez, how did I walk in those
pants? How
Speaker 20: did I do that? I don't even understand.
Speaker 21: How did I do
that? If
Speaker 21: anyone had the word can't use against them, it's me. I'm
a
Speaker 15: former gang member, I've committed crimes, I'm from the hood, black, obviously, tatted up,
Speaker 15: barely have
Speaker 21: a real education, and yet I was able to change my mindset and make a name for myself.
With this
Speaker 22: change of my mindset, I have become respected by scholars and also
Speaker 21: great influential people like Candace Owens.
Isaiah Washington, Rob Smith, hold on, this
Speaker 24: clicker ain't working too good for
Speaker 25: me today. I'm trying to be all professional and stuff. Angela
Staten King, who recently --
Who
Speaker 15: recently got a pardon from the president and is also running for Congress in Georgia. You go, girl. Where I'm at right here? I'm trying to be professional about reading and stuff. So I'm like,
you know, it's not
Speaker 15: working too good. I like the freestyle. We got Mark
Little.
This
Speaker 26: clicker thing, man, I'm looking in the front, I can't see it, but it's all right. We're going to make it work. Bryson Creates,
who also started the
Speaker 25: MAGA Challenge.
By
Speaker 25: the way, his mixtape is on all streaming platforms, by all means, go get that.
- Top of the charts!
Speaker 15: - Top of the charts, baby. David J. Harris.
Terrence K. Williams. That's my guy
Speaker 15: right there.
Speaker 15: Brandon Tatum.
By the way, congratulations
Speaker 15: with your engagement with Corrine. A woman that was with you shooting
in the gym. A woman
Speaker 15: that was with you shooting in the gym. It's well-deserved for her to bear your last name. Also, some of my other
Speaker 21: favorite people,
like... That's my
Speaker 28: favorite people right here. Check them
out.
Speaker 29: - Check 'em out.
Laura
Speaker 24: Trump, Eric Trump, and Don Jr., and of course, the man himself.
Yeah, yeah, that's
Speaker 30: me, that's
me.
Now imagine
Speaker 15: I allowed myself to be poisoned by the "cant" mentality. I wouldn't be standing on the stage in front of you amazing people and the thousands at home watching, allowing me to be the evidence my people need to see that they could be successful without selling drugs, committing crimes, being a
rapper, or playing sports.
That you can actually
Speaker 15: be successful in other avenues, like politics, where you can be put in positions to create real change in your communities that will help the masses, not just ourselves.
Speaker 21: But I'm sorry to say, we've also adopted another dangerous trait, which is selfishness.
We're real
Speaker 21: selfish, nobody
Speaker 31: wanted to give me no gum, my breath was hot, but it's
Speaker 15: alright. Everything is about ourselves, not each other.
Even
Speaker 15: back in the day, we as a community raised our kids. Your neighbor could see you doing something and your parents would know before you got home. And in some instances,
Speaker 21: you got your butt whip from your neighbors. I'm kind of happy that those days are over because I'm telling you, you touch
Speaker 25: my kid, it's pow, pow. You're out of here.
But the point
Speaker 15: is, we still need to police our own hoods. We are so selfish. We are so selfish, we even accuse other people of
Speaker 15: of it, because in our minds, if we don't give a damn, then how can anyone else give a damn? For example, when people see me advocating for a better mindset for my people, they assume it's because I'm getting paid. It's just about money. Make it as if I'm doing it for me, and it's not. It's not genuine. Wrong. My ultimate goal is to spread the truth. Not to say I wouldn't want to make any money if the opportunity presented
itself.
But I
Speaker 25: don't see anything wrong with getting paid to do what you love and support. Better yet, doing the right thing.
I made
Speaker 15: money most of my youth doing the wrong things. It's about time we popularize getting money doing the right thing.
But it's not about
Speaker 15: money.
Speaker 15: I do this for free, like I still am to this very day, so y'all send me some money. The reality is I'm doing this for our future. 'Cause if it was about me,
'cause if it was about me,
Speaker 15: I'd still be in the streets now, still making $25,000 to $5,000 a day doing the wrong thing. I'm doing what I'm doing now. I'm doing what I'm doing because I know it puts my people, which includes friends, family, white or black, but especially my black people.
and
Speaker 15: a better mindset, which will put us in the best position to win. We
need to
Speaker 15: focus on creating jobs and opportunities, but most importantly, bringing our families back together.
These are very important issues for our
Speaker 15: communities. These things will help us win.
Now, say it with
Speaker 24: me, y'all. Y'all can read, right?
Yeah.
Speaker 24: Win. Win. Win. One more time. Win. Win. Win. That's what I'm talking about, man. Y'all sound
Speaker 32: like some winners.
Now, let me
Speaker 33: get back to where I was at because I lost my place. Hold on a second. Let me see. Okay.
Speaker 35: Mindset successful. Okay. Hold on. Hold on a minute.
Speaker 35: Wait a minute, how did I lose my smile so fast? How did I do that, people? Okay, hold on. Ah, I
Speaker 36: found
it. That's the
Speaker 15: mindset we need in our community, the "I can win" mindset, which will put us in the path of being successful without having any excuses of why we can't, because many have, despite their
Speaker 21: circumstances,
Speaker 21: There's many examples of this. Let me give
you a few.
Speaker 30: You could win-- hold on,
let me
Speaker 30: make sure my peoples is here. There you go. That's my
guy. You could win and be
Speaker 15: successful like Ben Carson, who was the first surgeon to successfully separate conjoined twins that was connected from the back
of their heads. Hold on,
Speaker 25: let me go back. Let me go back. Let me go back.
Let me
Speaker 25: go back, I gotta go back. I told you, this clicker thing is new to me, baby. I'm just trying to work it. Don't mind
me.
Speaker 22: You could be successful like Rob Johnson, an entrepreneur, media magnet, and founder of BET.
I know. I know, I
Speaker 38: know. I know, I didn't want to put her up here, but I was
Speaker 25: like, why not, let's just.
Speaker 25: Let's just see where this goes.
You can
Speaker 22: win and be successful like Oprah.
Even though
Speaker 22: I'm not too fond of her these days, but she's still
Speaker 15: an example of what you can be when you apply yourself.
And not
Speaker 15: believing the I can't mentality.
I ain't even going to say no more
Speaker 20: because, you know, Oprah's been having a bad month.
She's been
Speaker 40: having a real bad
month. I hope y'all make that a
Speaker 41: meme. You can win and be successful like
Madam C.J. Walker.
who was
Speaker 15: considered the wealthiest black businesswoman at her time. And she did that during the time blacks wasn't welcomed as they are today.
Speaker 25: Okay. You could win and be successful like Frederick Douglass. A leader, writer, social reformer,
Speaker 42: and statesman who also accomplished these things during slavery times. Our people didn't believe in
Speaker 30: excuses back then,
huh?
wonder
Speaker 30: what happened. It's crazy. Maybe it's the media.
You
Speaker 41: could also be successful like our 44th
president. Don't, don't, don't do my man like
Speaker 43: that. I voted for him one
time.
I
Speaker 43: voted for him one
time. You could also
Speaker 41: be successful like our first black president,
Speaker 44: Donald J. Trump.
Speaker 44: He wouldn't look good, though, with the waves, right? You can't
even front. Y'all
Speaker 41: know they're going to chew me up for that one, right?
All right, now, settle down,
Speaker 25: settle down. I hope y'all got y'all
pictures.
Speaker 15: Anyway, all these people I mentioned have the I can mentality. They aren't better than you. They aren't more special than you. The only difference between you and them is they didn't believe in the
word can't.
Speaker 15: They are the I can people. But it
Speaker 41: saddens me that even our own black successful leaders are out here like race-baiting Al Sharpton. Hold on, hold on,
check them out.
Speaker 41: Check them
out.
This
Speaker 41: is not a Photoshop that is
Speaker 25: an actual selfie
They're telling
Speaker 25: you you can't do something because of the color your skin When they did it themselves that makes no sense
Speaker 30: you have people that call themselves scholars like a man at the baby called Jabari Y'all
could check
Speaker 15: him out on YouTube. I ain't a hater but anyway
They
Speaker 15: used their extensive knowledge of past atrocities in history to justify their attack on white people, instead of using that same knowledge to show our
Speaker 30: people what they have overcome. History is only good if you're using it
Speaker 22: proactively towards the future. Imagine our leaders was using history to say, "You could vote now. You could get a loan. You could have your own businesses. You could be a successful entrepreneur."
we
Speaker 15: would be in a better position. Me personally, I ignore the past because it means nothing in today's times. You can't move forward with one leg back stuck in the past. The can't mentality is a history of pain and the can't
Speaker 30: mentality is a history of progress.
Speaking of not letting
Speaker 15: your past determine your future, this reminds me of when I was
in sixth grade.
Check me
Speaker 30: out, I was cute. I was a big Bulls fan at that time. When I
was in
Speaker 15: sixth grade and my teacher Miss Romano said I wouldn't amount to nothing, that I can't make it in life because I was kind of like a bad apple, a jokester in school, and honestly kind of believed her. It shaped my life in
a way.
Speaker 15: It made me not care about doing the right things because it was like, what's the point? I ain't gonna be nothing anyway.
Speaker 15: which in many ways caused me not to even care about school, hence dropped out after eighth grade. I didn't see the point, which had me more involved with the streets,
Speaker 30: got into gangs, committed stupid crimes, but thankfully, that didn't get me any jail time or killed, 'cause those are usually the end results of living that negative
lifestyle. But
Speaker 15: let's pretend for a second that what they say is true, that you actually can't do something. How would you rather
live your life?
Speaker 15: The one life you have on this
earth.
Would you
Speaker 15: rather live your life thinking you can do something that you can't do or would you rather live your life thinking you can't do something that you actually can do and live with regret for not at least trying to accomplish your goals? I'd rather try and not succeed than do nothing and to live in regret. I'd rather live with a positive mentality
if you ask
Speaker 15: me. But this is a team effort.
The
Speaker 15: bottom line is, we need to work together, black and white, to create changes. We are Americans.
USA! USA! USA! USA! USA! Heh heh heh.
This is a
Speaker 31: non-profit y'all, let's be, let's be professional here, let's be professional. But y'all know
what time it is
Speaker 15: though. Just remember we're Americans and you can't
spell USA without
Speaker 15: us. We don't matter,
Speaker 39: it's us, remember
that.
Speaker 15: Anyway, I know y'all don't like to do long speeches. I like to get straight to the point. But let me leave y'all with this before
Speaker 30: y'all go to sleep tonight. I want you to think about who is your Miss Romano? Have you, who is your Miss Romano? The one that had you believing that you can't do something or did you make them a liar? 'Cause I definitely made Miss Romano a liar. You
can't tell?
Speaker 30: I'm on the stage.
Speaker 46: She lied to me.
Speaker 30: Anyway,
let me check my
Speaker 30: brother out. You know, I skipped that part. I want to thank my brother, my business partner, Jake Liddick, for putting this slide together. I want to thank Gina
Speaker 15: for dealing with my diva moments. I want to thank Larry Eldor for being a pioneer for this conservative
movement.
Oh, by the
Speaker 30: way, he's making me a movie star, too, because I'm in this movie coming out called Uncle Tom. That's
a perfect name,
Speaker 30: right? Because, you know, Uncle Tom was
the
Speaker 15: hero in that book, just for anybody that doesn't know. And
I want to
Speaker 15: thank everyone here and the people at home for having me today. Now, before I
Speaker 22: leave this stage, I need y'all to get up real quick and turn up with me. Come on, now, get up. Don't get lazy. Don't get lazy. Don't
get lazy.
Speaker 22: Keep them legs working. Now before I leave this stage,
Speaker 15: I need y'all to get up and turn up with me while we listen to someone I mentioned earlier. I love this song, and I want you to love it too. 'Cause remember, I'm doing this for the future. That's why I'm pro-life.
We have to save the
Speaker 25: babies. So let's welcome my bro Bryson Creates
to the stage.
Speaker 47: I love
Speaker 48: you.
Save
Speaker 49 (higher-pitched voice): the baby, save the baby, save the kids Have
a
Speaker 50 (higher-pitched voice): baby, let it grow and let it live I'ma keep it real cause my word is all I got Why that baby gotta suffer cause you was out here being a thot How you out here living your life and don't wanna save me for your seed How you go and take that life and be back out here on your knees But if your mama aborted you, how that statement make you feel You tell
me I'm being mean, I just think I'm being real If you say you don't wanna get pregnant, don't be
Speaker 51: out here busting it open And if you
don't
Speaker 51: I'm gonna bust it open and use a lifestyle or a trotin' Save the baby, save the baby, save the kids Have the baby let it grow,
just let it live Save the baby, save the baby, save the kids Have the
Speaker 49 (higher-pitched voice): baby let it grow and let
Speaker 52 (higher-pitched voice): it live Let me guess, you in school and you gotta save your bread Mm-hmm, yeah, you knew all that before you opened up them legs Oh, I hear you, it's not your fault Baby, you was just misled Mm-hmm,
cool, you should've thought
Speaker 52 (higher-pitched voice): about that But put it out in that bed If that don't hurt,
you know how.
Speaker 52 (higher-pitched voice): I work, hold on, where do I begin? You get to the doctor, he get the clamps Then he pull out baby limbs Go on Planned Parenthood site They donate organs to they friends Once you kill the baby, it's gone And it won't come back again Save the baby, save the baby, save the kids Have a baby, let it
grow, just let it live
Save
Speaker 49 (higher-pitched voice): the baby, save the baby, save the kids Have a baby, let it go and let it live